[Music]
AI agents have joined the global
workforce. NVIDIA IQ and Agentic AI
blueprint lets enterprises connect AI
agents to reasoning models and data
systems. Given a task, agent TJ needs to
reason, plan, iterate, and use tools to
generate a final
report. For example, what if I want to
research information for a board brief?
IQ uses NIM and Nemo to help TJ
synthesize hours worth of research in
minutes. Llama Neotron Super lets TJ
reason and has the capability to switch
its reasoning functionality on or off. A
single multi-purpose model. When on, the
model can find the best answer faster
than other similar reasoning models.
Nemo agent ops tools helps TJ process
information, adapt and learn. It can
ingest pabytes of data faster with
worldclass semantic query
accuracy. Nemo curates user and AI
feedback, then post- train small models
to exceed the accuracy of larger ones
for greater efficiency.
With the IQ blueprint, developers can
unlock the full potential of AI agents.
[Music]